lottery.com 2019-05-10

# Lottery Privacy - Powerball, Mega Millions | Lottery.com

Last updated: July 13, 2017

Lottery.com (“us”, “we”, “Lottery.com” or “our”) operates the [https://www.lottery.com](https://www.lottery.com/) website and the Lottery.com mobile application (the “Service”).

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at [https://www.lottery.com](https://www.lottery.com/).

Our Terms and Conditions are expressly incorporated herein by reference and made a part of this Privacy Policy.

 **Information Collection and Use**

For identification purposes, we collect certain personal information, and therefore, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your email address, physical address, age, name and date of birth. (“Personal Information”).

 **Log Data**

We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, general geographic information, and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to enhance our Service’s functionality. These third-party service providers have their own Privacy Policies addressing how they use such information.

When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, we may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile devices unique device ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use, and other statistics.

Lottery.com uses thirty party providers (“TPP”) to gather personal data and information. By using our Service, you grant Lottery.com the right, power, and authority to act on your behalf to access and transmit your personal and financial information from the relevant TPP. You agree to your personal and financial information being transferred, stored, and processed by TPPs in accordance with such TPP’s Privacy Policies.

 **Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

We use “cookies” to collect information. This information allows us to deliver a user experience that is more tailored to you. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some functionalities of our Service.

 **Do Not Track Disclosure**

Every attempt is made to honor your privacy preferences, however due to inconsistencies within industry standards, we currently are unable to support Do Not Track (“DNT”) requests from your browser. As the industry standards progress, we will re-evaluate our policy.

DNT is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

 **Service Providers**

We may employ third-party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

Should these third parties have access to your Personal Information, the sharing of said information will be limited strictly to the performance of tasks on our behalf and furthermore, they are legally and contractually prohibited from using and/or disclosing such information for any other purpose.

 **Communications**

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials, and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

 **Business Transaction**

If Lottery.com is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Information may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Information is transferred if it becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

 **Security**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, and therefore, we use commercially reasonable physical, administrative, and technological safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of all information collected through the Service. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use best practices to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

 **International Transfer**

Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to, and maintained on computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those in your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to the United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

 **Links to Other Sites**

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third-party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, Privacy Policies or practices of any third-party sites or services.

 **Minors’ Privacy**

Our Service does not allow access to anyone under the age of 18 (“minors”).

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from Minors. If you are a parent or guardian, and you are aware that your minor has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we discover that a minor under 18 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our servers immediately.

 **Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We will continue to evaluate this Privacy Policy against new technologies, business practices and our users’ needs, and may make changes to the Privacy Policy accordingly. Please check this page periodically for updates. You acknowledge that your continued use of our Services after the posting of any changes to this Privacy Policy means that you agree to be bound by such change.

 **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [contact us.](https://www.lottery.com/contact/)
